超过1.5万亿人在世界上，超过一半的人在24岁以下，经常观看短视频。
Mehr als 1,5 Billionen Menschen weltweit, über die Hälfte unter 24 Jahren, schauen regelmäßig kurze Videos.
短期內60秒或以下的片段，主要通过Snapchat、TikTok、Instagram Storys和其他智能手机应用程序。
Klips von 60 Sekunden oder weniger, mit Snapchat, TikTok, Instagram-Storys und anderen Smartphone-Apps.
2019年市场基本不存在。
The market barely existed 7 years ago.
然而，目前，创作者每天上传短视频总量达7020万。
Yet today, creators are uploading 702 million short videos every day.
随着我们的注意力span逐渐缩小到秒级，短视频不仅会长期存在，而且也将成为新常态。
As our attention span is falling to seconds, short video is not only here to stay, but will become the new normal.
与像Instagram这样的社交平台不同，完美编辑、打磨的图像是常见的，但短视频更具开放性，更倾向于接受缺陷和真实性。
Unlike other social platforms such as Instagram, where perfectly edited, polished images are the norm, short videos are more accessible, inviting imperfection and authenticity.
由于每个片段都很短，内容创作者必须具有创意和简洁的沟通能力。
And because each clip is so short, content producers have to be creative and concise communicators.
但这些小片段视频不仅仅是娱乐，而且有更深层次的意义。
But these bite-sized videos are more than just fun and entertainment.
对于我来说，作为咨询师和母亲，短视频就是我获取育儿建议的地方。
For me personally, as a consultant and mother, short videos are where I get parenting tips.
出差路上，我可以快速学习母乳喂养的 bí mật，了解如何在出行时提高产后恢复，获得如何让我的女儿睡眠更快的伟大想法。
On my way to work, I can quickly learn about the secrets of breastfeeding while travelling and get great ideas about how to make my daughter sleep sooner.
公司们也在学着，短视频是找到新客户和扩大观众多样性的一个非常好的手段。
Businesses are also learning that short videos is a great way to find new customers and expand the diversity of the audiences.
今年早些时候，我与TikTok，全球领先的短视频平台合作开展了一项项目，以评估这类小片段经济和社会影响。
Earlier this year, I led a project with TikTok, the world's leading short video platform, to assess the economic and social impact of this bite-sized economy.
我们的研究结果表明，这种年轻的媒体不仅仅是如何我们度过isure时间的变化，而且正在改变很多其他方面。
Our study shows that this young medium is changing a lot more than the way we spend our leisure time.
2019年，短视频市场估计产生了约950亿美元的商品和服务销售额，并创造了全球大约120万个就业机会。
In 2019, Short Video generated an estimated US$95 billion in goods and services sold and created roughly 1.2 million jobs globally.
即使短视频在很短的生命期内，已经对我们工作、沟通和学习方式产生了重大影响。
Even within its short lifespan, Short Video is already impacting the way we work, communicate and learn.
在COVID-19疫情期间，许多博物馆 worldwide在无意义的处理中停顿下來，但短视频已经迅速发展，产生了一种新鲜、年轻的出版形式。
In der Zeit der COVID-19-Krise, während Museums all over die Welt in unbedeutendem Umgang sind, haben viele schnell gearbeitet, eine neue, jüngere Publikation zu erledigen.
佛罗伦斯的乌菲齐美术馆，在三年前创建了其官方新网站，已经开始使用短视频，以发现新的出版物、了解其雕像和颜色。
Die Uffizi-Galerie in Florenz, die vor drei Jahren ihre offizielle neue Website erstellt hat, benutzt Short Video, um neue Publikationen zu entdecken, zu ihren Statuen und Farben.
它们使用具有Emoji、音乐歌词或幽默故事的展览，吸引观众。
Mit Exhibiten mit Emojis, Musiklyriken oder lustigen Wurzeln.
博物馆通过短视频使艺术作品更加容易被理解和相关，更适合年轻的艺术爱好者。
Das Museum macht das Kunstwerk mehr accessible und relevant für die jüngere Generation der Kunst-Liebenden.
在其最后一条文章中，发现了一个猫病毒被分离到一张-rok上并在一半被打破，靠近卡拉瓦乔的作品“美杜莎”，这位美杜莎有力量可以将那些在她身上移动的人凝视住。
In einem seiner letzten Posts wurde ein Katzen-Coronavirus in einen Rock getrennt und in der Hälfte geschlagen, vor Karavajos Kunstwerk Medusa, der die Macht hat, diejenigen, die sich auf sie in Stahl bewegen.
冠状病毒！
Coronavirus!
乌菲齐美术馆还与微博影响者进行了对live streaming从gallery的短视频平台实验，为了让世界各地的观众体验到他们在人间还 nunca看到过的事情。
Uffizi hat auch mit Influencers Live Streaming von der Galerie auf einer kurzen Videoplattform experimentiert, um die Zuschauer weltweit zu erleben, was sie in Person noch nie gesehen haben.
自April 2020年开始关注TikTok以来，博物馆的社交媒体账户已在三个月内获得超过4.3万名粉丝。
Seit seiner Aufmerksamkeit auf TikTok im April 2020 hat das Museumsprofil mehr als 43.000 Follower in drei Monaten getroffen.
速度远快于他们在Twitter上的旅行，过去四年来也建立了类似的粉丝基数。
Die Geschwindigkeit ist viel schneller als ihre Reise auf Twitter, wo es in den letzten vier Jahren ein ähnliches Niveau von Fanbase gebaut hat.
小型企业也利用短视频作为发现新的观众的方法，可能从未听说过他们或他们产品。
Small businesses are also using short video as a way to find new audiences who might have never heard of them or their products before.
2018年，中国最具影响力的短视频平台之一Douyin作为其社会责任倡议的一部分，以减轻中国贫困问题而推出了一个帮助中国山区个体农民和小型企业出售农作物的活动。
In 2018, Douyin, the leading Chinese short video platform as part of its social responsibility initiative to alleviate poverty in China, launched a campaign to help individual farmers and small businesses in China's mountainous area sell farm produce.
作为其试验项目之一，Douyin邀请内容创作者制作四个15秒的短视频，以展示他们产品的质量。
As one of its pilot projects, Douyin invited content producers to create four pieces of 15-second short videos, showcasing the quality of their products.
这还包括其他常规的公共关系活动，如宣传文章等。
This is on top of other regular PR initiatives such as promotional articles.
他们希望利用短视频的庞大用户基数找到可能对这些产品感兴趣的人，然后将它们与电子商务网站连接起来，让人们可以在观看视频时购买东西。
They wanted to leverage the large user base of short video to find those customers who might be interested in those products, and then connected them with the e-commerce website so that people can buy things as they watch the videos.
仅仅五天内，这项活动帮助四川省近4000家家庭出售了令人震惊的120000公斤葡萄。
In just five days, the initiative helped nearly 4,000 families in Sichuan province sell an astonishing 120,000 kg of plums.
许多想要招募和雇佣年轻人的人都在使用短视频作为与世代Z互动的一种新鲜方法。例如，麦当劳的员工中有超过半数年龄在16岁至24岁之间。
Many brands that are interested in hiring and recruiting young people have been using short video as a fresh way to engage with Generation Z. For example, more than half of McDonald's employees are aged between 16 to 24.
澳大利亚是一个年轻人短缺的市场，行业在过去几年一直在招募人手上苦战。
In Australien war die Branche in den vergangenen Jahren in der Rekrutierung zu kämpfen.
她还提到了snap应用。
Also hat sie etwas genannt, den Snap-Applikation.
这是一个snapchat线程，向客户推送10秒的视频，展示他们为什么是理想的麦当劳员工，并提供求职链接。
Das ist eine Snapchat-Linie, die den Kunden zehn Sekunden Videos schiebt, die zeigen, warum sie ein perfekter McDonalds-Employee sind, und dann die Link-of-Job-Applikation anbieten.
在推出这一项Campaign后仅24小时内，麦当劳获得了3000个snap应用。
Nach 24 Stunden nach dem Launchen der Kampagne hat McDonalds 3000 Snap-Applikationen bekommen.
比他们通过传统方法在整个星期获得的数量四倍多。
viermal mehr als die Zahl, die sie in der ganzen Woche durch traditionelle Methoden bekommen haben.
然而，人们不确定短视频是否是找到正确的人员或拯救有才华的最佳方式。
Es ist unklar, ob ein kurzes Video als der beste Weg zu finden, die richtigen Leute für den Job zu finden oder Talent zu retten.
但只凭他们招募的人数，推广活动才能成为全球热门。
Aber nur durch die Numeren, die sie rekrutiert haben, war die Kampagne ein globaler Hitsch.
在沙特阿拉伯，麦当劳在24小时内获得了4.3万个snap应用。
In Saudi-Arabien hat McDonalds in 24 Stunden 43.000 Snack-Applikationen bekommen.
并且公司再次推出该项目，后来在美国展开。
und die Firma eröffnete die Kampagne wieder, später in den USA.
无论如何，我希望从短视频父母那里获得一些建议。
Wie auch immer, möchte ich von Short Video Parenthood Tipps bekommen.
许多观众也想学习这项平台，但希望以小片段、双端的形式来呈现。
Viele Zuschauer wollen auch, die Plattform zu lernen, aber in kleinen, beidseiten Dosen.
在我们的研究中，短视频观众是全球平台的顶级好处，他们能够发现新的兴趣和新技能。
In unserem Studium sind Short Video Zuschauer weltweit die Top-Benefiz der Plattform, die neue Interessen und neue Fähigkeiten entdecken.
在这一市场中，特别是短视频对于教育和培训具有巨大的潜力，可以改变现状。
In der erheblichen Marktart besonders, das kurze Video für Unterricht und Bildung hat große Potenziale, den Status quo zu verändern.
2019年，TikTok在印度推出了一项Campaign，旨在通过民主教育方式，为印度的数字社区提供教育。
In 2019 launchte TikTok eine Kampagne in Indien mit dem Ziel der demokratisierenden Unterrichtung für die indische digitale Gemeinschaft.
自从应用于该地区以来，自2020年7月起，该应用在这些国家的使用人数迅速增长，并且为创意短视频联系开启了一个大型调查，并且推出了其他平台。
Während der App seit Juli 2020 in den Ländern verbunden ist, hat er eine große Befragung für kreative, kurze Video-Kontakte eröffnet und andere Plattformen in den Raum gefüllt sind.
TikTok有机会推广这个趋势，通过与印度社会企业、公共启动公司和流行创意人合作，生产15秒的短视频，它们涵盖了各种主题。
TikTok hat die Chance, diesen Trend aufzuwenden, indem man mit indischen sozialen Unternehmen, Öffentlichkeits-Start-ups und populären Kreatoren zusammenarbeitet, um 15 Sekunden kurze Videos zu produzieren, die eine Reihe von Themen ausüben.
从小学科学到学习新的语言。
Von Schule-Level-Science zu neuen Sprachen zu lernen.
随着短视频的第一波在平台上广泛传播，观众被激发，并且有一些人甚至开始创建自己的教育内容。
As the first wave of short video became widely spread on the platform, audiences got inspired, and some even began to create their own educational content.
到了2019年10月，Campaign已经产生了超过1亿短视频，并获得了48亿次观看。
By October 2019, the campaign had generated more than 10 million videos and garnered 48 billion views.
通过帮助人们学习和参与到内容创作的过程中，短视频实际上是在为未来挑战中的有才华的人群做准备并进行培训。
Through helping people learn and participate into the process of content creation, short videos are in fact helping prep and train the skilled population that can take on the challenges of the future.
像所有社交媒体一样，短视频平台也存在一些合理的担忧。
Like all social media, there are valid concerns around short video platforms.
包括数据隐私、这种格式的易受依赖性以及内容中缺乏细节和背景等问题。
Including data privacy, the addictive nature of the format and the lack of nuance and context in the content.
然而，我仍然认为短视频的积极结果将超过其负面影响。
However, I still think that the positive outcomes of short video will outweigh its downsize.
我相信短视频将成为未来经济和社会力量的更重要组成部分。
I believe short video will become a more vital economic and social force in the future.
正是因为这样，我们需要找到通过用户、平台和政策制定者之间的合作来从这个年轻媒体中受益的正确方式。
It is precisely because of this that we need to find the right way to benefit from this young medium through collaboration among users, platforms and policy makers.
感谢。
Thank you.